igraciousliving.com 2013-05-16

# iGraciousLiving-Privacy-Policy

## iGraciousLiving.com and Lugen Family Office Inc. – Policy Respecting Your Privacy and the Protection of Personal Information

At Lugen Family Office Inc., we are privileged each and every day to help members achieve their goals and to empower their family and business legacies. We understand the need to protect the personal information you provide to us and we take this role very seriously. Our commitment to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is addressed in this privacy policy. Our policy complies with the requirements of the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.

## Electronic Documents Act of Canada

We want you to understand why we need your personal information, how the confidentiality of this information is protected, and how you can find out what information concerning you is recorded. This policy applies to all iGraciousLiving.com memberships.

## Accountability

In order to provide you with the highest levels of security, Lugen Family Office Inc. has retained highly respectable third party providers to securely store your personal information. For your security protection, we have included in our Appendix the privacy policies of these third party providers for your review. We have appointed a Chief Privacy Officer who is accountable for the membership compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please refer to the last page of this policy for information on how to contact our Chief Privacy Officer.

## Personal Information

Personal information is information that can be used to identify and/or contact you as an individual. This includes such information as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, banking information, credit card number, and the like. Payment information provided to Lugen Family Office Inc. will not be retained by us. Only our payment processing vendor will collect your credit card information.

## Purposes

Lugen Family Office Inc. collects personal information for the following purposes: 

  * to understand your personal, family, and business situation, as well as other related lifestyle, business, and financial needs and objectives, so that we can assist you in achieving them;
  * to determine your eligibility for membership and for ordering our products and services;
  * to process your membership payments and to ensure that your account remains up-to-date. However, your credit card, or other payment information, is not stored on our site and we do not have access to this information;
  * to invite you to participate in member surveys or other opinion-gathering devices that assist us in making your membership more responsive to your needs;
  * to inform you of various matters relating to your membership and about our products and services that we believe may be of interest to you;
  * to request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Web site and our publications, products and services;
  * to conduct marketing analysis, to send you surveys or newsletters, to contact you about services, products, activities, special events or offers from Lugen Family Office Inc. or our partners and for other marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes; 
  * to send you a welcoming email and to contact you about your use of the Web site and services; to respond to your emails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints; to perform after-sales services; to anticipate and resolve problems with our service; to respond to customer support inquiries, for assistance with our product and service development; and to inform you of updates to products and services from Lugen Family Office Inc., or our strategic partners, that better meet your needs;
  * to store contacts you enter or upload into your contacts list for your private use and viewing;
  * to send emails to users you invite (and contacts you invite to become users);
  * to enable you to communicate, collaborate, and share files with users you designate;
  * to contact you if you win a contest; and
  * for other purposes about which we notify you.

Lugen Family Office Inc. may also collect information regarding the frequency of your visits to its sites and about the specific products and services that you take advantage of, so that we may constantly strive to offer you the best range of family, lifestyle, financial, and business options. 

Lugen Family Office Inc. wants to hear from its members regarding any issues or comments they may have with respect to their memberships or any products or services offered by iGraciousLiving.com. We may record this information and transmit it to our affiliates, and our strategic network of product and service providers, in order to have them address your concerns in the appropriate manner.

We may also combine your personal information with that of other individuals to create aggregate data which we will use, for example, to improve our products and services and develop new ones. Aggregate data, is general information about groups of customers but not about you as an individual.  
We will not use or disclose your personal information for any purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required or authorized by law.

## Consent

Your knowledge and consent are required for the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. When you become a member of iGraciousLiving.com and Lugen Family Office Inc., you consent to the use of your personal information for the purposes listed above. You may refuse or withdraw your consent at any time; however, we may not then be able to provide you with our full range of services. We will advise you when you refuse or withdraw your consent of the impact this decision will have on what we are able to provide. For information on withdrawing your consent, please contact our Chief Privacy Officer.

## Third-party disclosure

Lugen Family Office Inc. is not in the business of selling member information to others. We do contract with trusted companies to act on our behalf to fulfill certain functions. The names, addresses, emails, and telephone numbers of our customers may be transmitted to a third-party mailing or broadcasting services in order to inform you of products and services that we offer (or that we and our partners jointly offer) and that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also provide information to a reputable third-party advertising company for the purpose of developing future campaigns and gathering survey information. We will take steps to ensure that such parties adhere to our policy with respect to the protection of your personal information.

Except as set out in this policy, or as required by law, Lugen Family Office Inc. will not sell or disclose any of your personal information to any other organization or transmit personal information to third parties without first obtaining your consent.

Lugen Family Office inc. may, however, disclose information in the following cases: 

  * to our lawyer
  * to a police force, if required by law
  * to a person authorized by a law or collective agreement
  * to a government agency that can oblige us to do so in emergency situations in which life, health or safety of a member is in danger
  * to all other persons authorized by law or to an agent retained by Lugen Family Office Inc. in connection with the collection of your account

## Retention

We will only retain your personal information as long as is necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected or as required by law. Personal information is stored in a secure facility until such time as it is no longer required, after which it is destroyed.

## Accuracy

Lugen Family Office Inc. strives to maintain the accuracy and completeness of your personal information. You may ask us to delete or correct information contained in your file. The request for correction must be made in writing to our Chief Privacy Officer, at the address below.

## Safeguards

Your personal information is secure within Lugen Family Office Inc. and iGraciousLiving.com. We have comprehensive security controls to protect against unauthorized access, use, alteration, duplication, destruction or disclosure. We protect your personal information by using safeguards that are appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. Each of our employees is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of all personal information to which they have access. We keep our employees informed about our policies and procedures for protecting personal information. Where necessary, our employees are required to sign agreements to keep your personal information confidential.

## Member Access

In order to fulfill requests for personal information records or to answer any questions or address any concerns individuals may have about privacy, Lugen Family Office Inc. has designated a Chief Privacy Officer. In addition to answering inquiries, the Chief Privacy Officer is also responsible for ensuring that the Policy requirements and related procedures are being met.

All inquiries or complaints regarding privacy should be directed in writing to the Chief Privacy Officer by mail, FAX or email at the addresses below. All inquiries will be responded to within thirty (30) days from the date on which our Chief Privacy Officer has received the inquiry. Lugen Family Office Inc. can refuse access to a file in certain circumstances.

MAIL FAX EMAIL  
Lugen Family Office Inc. c/o Chief Privacy Officer   
880, 505 Burrard St., Box 43, Vancouver, BC, V7X 1M4   
FAX: (604) 913-3687

## Amendments to Our Privacy Policy

Lugen Family Office Inc. may review and revise this privacy policy from time to time at its discretion. Changes to this policy will be posted on iGraciousLiving.com and you are encouraged to review this policy whenever you are on our site.

**APPENDIX**

**Box.net Privacy Policy**  
(Last Updated: August 11, 2009)

Your privacy is important to Box.net. This privacy policy (“Policy”) applies to the Box.net Web sites and services and tells you how personal information is collected, used, disclosed, and protected by Box.net. This statement includes both Box.net’s European Union - U.S. Safe Harbor Privacy Statement and the Website Privacy Statements.

## Changes to This Policy

We may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “last updated” date above. If there are material changes to this Policy, we will notify you more directly. We encourage you to check this Policy whenever you use our Web sites and services to understand how your personal information is used.

## Information Collected

We collect information from you in various ways when you use our Web sites and services. We may also supplement this information with information from other companies. We collect two general types of information, namely personal information and aggregate data. As used in this Policy, the term “personal information” means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name and email address), and demographic and other information when directly linked to information that can identify an individual. 

Our definition of personal information does not include “aggregate” data. Aggregate data is information we collect about a group or category of services or users from which individual user identities have been removed. In other words, no personal information is included in aggregate data. Aggregate data helps us understand trends in our users’ needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our services. This Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate data, and we may share aggregate data about our users with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customer needs and improve our services and for advertising and marketing purposes. 

The following are the specific types of information we collect from you. 

  * Information You Give Us. We collect information you give us on our Web site and when you register for and use our services. Examples include the following: 
  * Registration and Profile Information. When you register to use our services or update your profile, we may collect various kinds of information about you including, your name and email address; your title, company and other profile information you provide; demographic information; and information you upload like photos, files, and documents. 
  * Contact Information. We collect the email addresses you provide for contacts you enter or upload into your private contacts page. When you choose to collaborate or share files with others, we also collect email addresses you provide to email invitations to those individuals on your behalf. 
  * Payment Information. If you choose to use a paid Box.net account or service, our payment processing vendor collects your credit card information and billing address. 
  * Submissions and Customer Service. From time to time we may use surveys, contests or sweepstakes requesting personal or demographic information and customer feedback. 
  * Automatically Collected Information. We automatically receive certain types of information when you interact with our Web pages, services and communications. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Web site you visit, including ours. That information includes your computer’s IP address, access times, your browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about the type of operating system you use, your account activity, and files and pages accessed or used by you. 
  * Cookies and Web Beacons. We may also use certain kinds of technology such as cookies and Web beacons to collect information. Among other things, the use of cookies and Web beacons enables us to improve our Web sites and emails by seeing which areas and features are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing our Web site, to personalize and improve your experience, to record your preferences, and to allow you to visit our Web site without re-entering your member ID and/or password. A cookie is a small amount of data which is sent to your browser from a Web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You can modify your browser setting to reject our cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie by editing your browser options. However, if a browser is set not to accept cookies or if a user rejects a cookie, some portions of the Web site and services may not function properly. For example, you may not be able to sign in and access certain Web page features or services. A Web beacon is an electronic image, also called a "gif," that may be used on our Web pages to deliver cookies, count visits and compile statistics on usage and campaign effectiveness or in our emails to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

## Use of Personal Information.

In general, we use your personal information to process your requests or transactions, to provide you with information or services you request, to inform you about other information, events, promotions, products or services we think will be of interest to you, to facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Web site and services and to otherwise serve you and our users. For example, we may use your personal information:

  * to request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Web site and our publications, products and services;
  * to conduct marketing analysis, to send you surveys or newsletters, to contact you about services, products, activities, special events or offers from Box.net or our partners and for other marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes; 
  * to send you a welcoming email and to contact you about your use of the Web site and services; to respond to your emails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints; to perform after-sales services; to anticipate and resolve problems with our service; to respond to customer support inquiries, for assistance with our product and service development; and to inform you of updates to products and services from Box.net that better meet your needs; 
  * to store contacts you enter or upload into your contacts list for your private use and viewing; 
  * to send emails to users you invite (and contacts you invite to become users) to collaborate and access your files; 
  * to enable you to communicate, collaborate, and share files with users you designate; 
  * to contact you if you win a contest; and 
  * for other purposes about which we notify you.

Box.net may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. Box.net adheres to the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor privacy principles regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from the European Union. Box.net’s Safe Harbor certification can be found at [http:/web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/shlist.nsf/webPages/safe+harbor+list](http://www.igraciousliving.com/web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/shlist.nsf/webPages/safe+harbor+list). For more information about the Safe Harbor Principles, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Website at <http://export.gov/safeharbor/>.

## Sharing of Personal Information.

Box.net reserves the right to share aggregated demographic information about our customers, sales, and traffic to our partners and advertisers. We will not give, sell, rent, share, or trade any of your personal information or any data that you store using our services to any third party except as outlined in this Policy or with your consent. We may disclose information to a third party to (a) comply with laws or respond to lawful requests and legal process, (b) to protect Box.net, agents, customers, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use or (c) in the good faith belief that disclosure is needed to respond to an emergency, or protect the personal safety of any person. 

Box.net includes collaboration features that by their nature support sharing with users you choose. Those users can see your name, email address, photo and information from your Profile page, and any files you choose to share; and they can post comments and email you. Collaborators you invite as editors can also edit your shared files, upload documents and photos to your shared files, share those documents outside of Box.net, and give other users rights to view your shared files. 

Box.net provides you with opportunities to connect with third party services, such as through our Open Box page. If you choose to use any such third party services, we may facilitate sharing of your information and documents you choose to use with those services. Your use of such services is not governed by Box.net’s terms or privacy policy. Box.net does not control the services of those third parties or how they use your information and documents. Be sure to review the terms and the privacy policies of those third parties before using their services. 

We may share personal information in connection with an acquisition, merger, or sale of all or a substantial portion of our business, with or to another company. In any such event, you will receive notice if your data is transferred and becomes subject to a substantially different privacy policy.

## Network and Information Security.

Box.net takes reasonable steps to protect information we collect from you to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. In addition, highly confidential personal information such as credit card number and password that we request from you on our Web site is protected with encryption, such as Secured Socket Layer (SLL) protocol, during transmission over the Internet. 

The servers on which information is stored are kept in a controlled environment with limited access. While we take reasonable efforts to guard personal information we knowingly collect directly from you, no security system is impenetrable. In addition, we cannot guarantee that any passively-collected personal information you choose to include in documents you store on our systems are maintained at adequate levels of protection to meet specific needs or obligations you may have relating to that information. 

Your account information and access to our service is accessible only through the use of an individual user ID and password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused. In addition, always logout and close your browser when you finish your session. Please note that we will never ask you to disclose your password in an unsolicited phone call or email.

## Updating and Accessing Personal Information.

If your personal information changes in any way, we invite you to correct or update your information as soon as possible. You can make updates to your profile information by logging into your account on Box.net at any time. You can also request changes or access to your information by emailing support@box.net.

## Choice/Opt-Out.

Box.net may send you communications or data regarding our Web sites and services, including but not limited to (i) notices about your use of our Web sites and services, including any notices concerning violations of use, (ii) updates, and (iii) promotional information and materials regarding our products and services. You may opt-out of receiving promotional emails from Box.net by following the opt-out instructions provided in those emails. You may also opt-out of receiving promotional emails and other promotional communications from us at any time by emailing support@box.net with your specific request. Opt-out requests will not apply to transactional service messages, such as security alerts and notices about your current account and services.

## Enforcement

If you have any questions about this Policy, you should first contact us at support@box.net. If you do not receive a response or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with Box.net to resolve your concerns.

## Contacting Us

Any questions about this Policy should be addressed to support@box.net .

**Plan Your Legacy Privacy Policy**

We appreciate the trust you place in Plan Your Legacy and we are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the MyBreadcrumbs.com site (the 'Site'). By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement. The use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy posted on the website at the time of use, regardless if this policy should change.

## Collection and Use of Information

We are serious about protecting our member's personal information. Any personal information you provide will be used only to communicate with you and to provide the services that you request. We will not disclose any non-public personal information except to the extent you have instructed us to do so. We may use information to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use, but these statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any information that could identify you personally.

## Release of Information

Your information will not be released to any third party for a mailing list. We do not sell member information to other parties. Member information is shared only in the following circumstances: 

  * Agents: We may contract with other companies to perform certain functions on our behalf, such as processing credit card payments and providing customer service. They will have access to information only to the extent necessary to perform their functions, and are restricted from using it for other purposes. 
  * Legal Protection: We may release information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with law, enforce our agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of others. 
  * Business Transfers: In the unlikely event that we are acquired or if substantially all of our assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 
  * Trusted Affiliates: We may occasionally release contact information to trusted affiliates who may use the information solely to contact you regarding products or services which may be of interest to you. 
  * With Your Consent: We will release information as instructed by you. Other than as set forth herein, you will receive notice when personal information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

## Security

We have adopted physical and technological processes and procedures to keep your personal information safe and secure. The personal information you provide when you establish an account or place an order is secured using Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption technology. We use this SSL technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet to our own servers. As additional security, the contents of your interactive Survivor Assistance Journal is encrypted when it is collected and is always stored in an encrypted format until it is authorized by you to be released

## Cookies

Like most websites, we use 'cookies' to collect certain types of information about you, which we use to analyze the usage of our site and help improve operation of our site. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Certain features may be only available through the use of a cookie.

## E-mail Communications

If you provide us with your e-mail address, we may send you emails to provide you services or respond to a request. We may also send you occasional promotional emails which may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive promotional emails, you may opt out by contacting us at [question@planyourlegacy.com](mailto:question@planyourlegacy.com)

## Children

We do not provide services designed for use by children. If you are under 18, you should not submit any personal information to us. Please email any concerns or questions to [question@planyourlegacy.com](mailto:question@planyourlegacy.com)

**Beanstream's Privacy Policy**

## The Collection and Use of Information

Beanstream limits the information we collect about our customers and potential customers to what we need for internal business purposes only. We obtain your consent if we wish to use your information for any other purpose and before collecting information from third parties such as credit bureaus. 

Beanstream understands that privacy is a critical issue for all our customers and is committed to protecting customer personal information. We want to earn our customers’ trust by providing safeguards to protect personal information as we continue to provide valuable products and services. 

Beanstream's Privacy Policy is designed to comply with Canada’s federal Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act including the ten principles set out in the National Canadian Standards Association: Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information. Based on these guidelines and Beanstream's Best Business Practices, ten privacy principles have been customized to meet the specific needs and expectations of our customers. 

The Privacy Policy at Beanstream is a formal statement that outlines the minimum requirements for the protection of personal information. The objectives of the Privacy Policy are to promote responsible management of personal information, and to inform our customers of our practices. 

Beanstream will continue to review this Privacy Policy to ensure it remains current with changing laws and regulations while meeting the evolving needs of customers. In the event of any amendment to the Privacy Policy, a notice will be posted within this page.

## Privacy Statement

Beanstream recognizes the importance of respecting customers’ right to privacy and adheres to the following key principles: 

  * Beanstream is responsible for personal information under its control and has designated individuals to be accountable for the organization’s compliance. 
  * The purposes for which personal information is collected will be identified at or before the time the information is collected. 
  * Knowledge and consent will be obtained for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information, except where deemed inappropriate. 
  * The collection of personal information is limited to that which is related to the purposes identified by Beanstream. 
  * Personal information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the customer or as required by law. 
  * Reasonable efforts will be made to ensure that personal information is as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used. 
  * Personal information will be protected by reasonable security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the personal information. 
  * Information is available to customers regarding Beanstream’s policies and procedures relating to the management of personal information. 
  * Upon request, and within a reasonable period of time, a customer will be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of his or her personal information and will be given access to that information. A customer is entitled to comment on the accuracy and completeness of his or her personal information, and have that information amended where appropriate. 
  * A customer can address a challenge concerning compliance with the above principles to Beanstream’s designated Privacy Officer. 

## Privacy Officer

Beanstream Internet Commerce Inc   
302-2659 Douglas St   
Victoria, BC, V8T 4M3   
privacyofficer@beanstream.com

## Information Release

Beanstream does not arbitrarily sell or trade identifiable client information to third parties. Release of your information occurs only 

  * where we have your consent; or 
  * to our suppliers or agents who assist us in serving you; or 
  * where we are required or permitted to do so by law. 

## Protecting Information

We protect your information with appropriate safeguards and security measures and we retain your information only for the time it is required for the purposes we stated. Only those employees involved in processing data have access to this data. Any employee found in violation of our security or privacy policies is subject to disciplinary action.

## Use of Cookies

Beanstream does not employ cookies with the exception of those merchants, who have elected to use our shopping cart service, use cookies to track items added to the shopping cart when you make a purchase. Merchants have the option of disabling this feature and using their own session tracking. 

If you are a merchant registered on our system, a session identification is generated whenever you log into the membership area. This session ID tracks your movement through our system but does not store any information on your hard drive.

## Email Address and Contact Information

When you send us e-mail or when you ask us to respond to you by email, we learn your exact email address and any information you have included in the email. We use your email address to acknowledge your comments and/or reply to your questions, and we may store your communication and our reply in case we need to correspond further. 

On certain pages we provide users the option of submitting names, addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers and email addresses for the purpose of contacting you for sales or support follow-up. This data is not shared with anyone outside of our organization other than our suppliers or agents who assist us in serving you or where we are required or permitted to do so by law.

## Access to Credit Card Information

We restrict access to credit card information, and credit card numbers are not provided to merchants. In the event of a customer complaint or chargeback, transaction information will be provided to the merchant, bank or card issuer. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our implementation, please contact us to discuss your needs or concerns.

**Infusionsoft Privacy Policy **

## Customer Information:

All Infusionsoft customer account information is held confidential. We do not sell our customer list or customer information. Customer information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number, fax number and billing information is collected for the sole purpose of providing services to our customers and notifying them of improvements to our products and services.

From time to time, we will send special offers and promotional notices via mail, email, fax, and/or voice broadcast to our customers and to prospects who have expressed interest and have requested such information. At any time, customers may opt-out of such offers and notifications by following the opt-out link on the specific communication or by contacting Infusionsoft directly.

## Customer Lead Information

All leads generated by our customers and data stored for our customers are held and protected in strict confidence. Infusionsoft does not contact customer leads, nor do we sell or share customers' lead information with any other party.

## Affiliate Information

All Infusionsoft affiliate information is confidential. This information is collected for the purposes of: 1) generating commission checks and 2) complying with United States federal tax requirements.

## Contact Us

Main Phone: 866.800.0004   
Main Fax: 480.391.8177   
Mailing Address:   
2065 W. Obispo Ave.   
Suite 103   
Gilbert, AZ 85233

At www.iGraciousLiving.com there is a separate membership category referred to as the “Junior Member”. When a child registers on our website as a Junior Member, a notification letter is automatically sent out to the parent or guardian’s e-mail address that was provided by the child at the time of registration. Junior Membership applies to children ages 12 years and younger. At the time of registration, the child is instructed to ask for his or her parent/guardian’s permission before s/he submits his or her registration request. Junior Membership to www.iGraciousLiving.com is free and allows children 12 years of age and younger to view educational and inspirational materials, such as videos, games, and links to other child-centered websites. 

In order to register as a ”Junior Member”, a child must provide us with the following information: 

  * First Name  

  * Last Name   

  * Country (to determine legal jurisdiction)  

  * Child’s e-mail Address  

  * User Name (chosen by your child)  

  * Password (chosen by your child)  

  * Birth Year (to determine age group)  

  * Parent /Guardian’s e-mail address (to send notification to parent/guardian) 

As part of our ongoing desire to assist families in teaching their core values to their children, we encourage parents/guardians, together with their child, to review the Junior Members’ content on the www.iGraciousLiving.com website.

Since we take our fiduciary responsibility of protecting children seriously, we do not sell any products or services to our Junior Members, nor do we contact them beyond their first (and only) e-mail where they are welcomed as a Junior Member and required to confirm their registration request. Children’s registration information is securely maintained within our database and will not be rented, sold, or disclosed to any other organization, nor will it be transmitted to third parties, unless required by law. We do not collect any other information from children, directly or indirectly. 

Only those among our staff who need access to a child’s information in order to do their jobs, and our contractors assisting us in the programming and maintenance of the website, are allowed access. Anyone who fails to comply with our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and/or the institution of civil or criminal proceedings. 

## Live Chat with iGraciousLiving.com Staff

Upon a child’s initiation only, and upon his or her request to engage one of our staff in a live chat, will we be in contact with your child. Live chats will be limited to basic pleasantries and answering your child’s questions. Live chats with our members are made possible through BoldChat software. The child’s name, along with his or her chat transcripts, are saved indefinitely on BoldChat’s servers. BoldChat’s data center is located in San Antonio, Texas. No other information is collected during these engagements.

## Revoking a Child’s Access

If a parent/guardian wishes to unsubscribe their child from our website, they are instructed to complete the unsubscribe form accessible through a special link located within the parent/guardian’s notification letter. The child’s access to our website will be revoked immediately and his or her registration information, as listed above, will be permanently deleted from our database. When a parent/guardian fills out the unsubscribe form, it is vital that s/he uses the exact identification data that was used when his or her child registered. For the parent/guardian’s convenience, the information required to unsubscribe the child is provided within the parent/guardian’s notification letter. 

## Links To Other Sites

The iGraciousLiving.com website contains links to other sites that we do not control. These other sites may send their own cookies, collect data, or solicit personal information. We cannot accept responsibility for any failure on their part to comply with the terms of our [Privacy Policy](http://www.igraciousliving.com/igraciousliving-privacy-policy) or with any relevant legal requirements. Although we endeavor to select only those links that are child friendly, we cannot guarantee that all the materials on these other websites are suitable for children.

Please note that the iGraciousLiving.com Children’s Privacy Policy applies to all children (12 years of age and younger) and is in addition to the [iGraciousLiving.com Privacy Policy](http://www.igraciousliving.com/igraciousliving-privacy-policy). 

If you have any questions or comments about our Children’s Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:

iGraciousLiving.com   
Operated by Lugen Family Office Inc.  
c/o Chief Privacy Officer  
Suite 880, 505 Burrard St., Box 43  
Vancouver, BC V7X 1M4 Canada   
Ph: 1 (866) 605-8885  
Fx: (604) 913-3687  
e-mail: [privacyofficer@igraciousliving.com](mailto:privacyofficer@igraciousliving.com)
